gwen filming yep awesome hey everybody
ben tennyson here and this is epic
skateboarding alien style
let's do this
one
two
epic
whoops got this reversed
that's better
go ahead ben hey everybody ben tennyson
here to show you how to do the perfect
cannonball using cannon bolt
all right here we go
cut
filming check
matching wristbands and headband check
treadmill check
now to set up a new speed record
warming up
going fast
faster than a locomotive
faster than lightning new record here i
come
[Music]
unpredictable alien watch timing out
check
ouch
here's the cousin challenge i'll do
gwen's chores for a week for every time
she hits wild vine with a water balloon
but if she doesn't hit me at all i am
awesome
yeah no way those water balloons get
past these vinys i'll swap those away
like hey come on move on little guy i
said beat it you crazy little bird
yeah no george for two months yeah so
not awesome
welcome to the first ever tennyson
jumping contest on this side we have the
lively grandpa max and of course you got
me ben tennyson okay go
looks like we have a winner wait wait
grandpa max is taller this isn't fair
seriously ben here's round two of the
tennyson jumping contest
thanks for watching
huh that's a really big water slide
why are you staring at me
after much pleading and promising to
actually do my chores grandpa max has
agreed to test out the epic shiny water
slide
with the help of overflow oh wait but i
don't need any
[Music]
i'm sure he's fine not only is grandpa
max an amazing water slide tester but
he's also a world-class belly flopper
who knew
here we go
[Music]
ha
today's dancing with diamond head i'm
going to show you how to dust it off
feeling the beat oh yeah and here we go
dust it off dust it off dust it off it's
on the wrist yeah i'm killing it
[Music]
grandpa will never find out
this concludes dancing with diamond head
thanks for watching
[Music]
you